(Sheldon:)Would you like to play one?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Oh, come on, it's fun.
Whoo! Another bump.
Okay. Uh, I'll say an element
and, uh, you say an element...
(Sheldon:)...whose name starts
with the last letter of the one I said, okay?
(Sheldon:)I'll start.
"Helium."
Now, you could say, "Mercury."
(Sheldon:)That would give me a Y.
Ooh, very clever. That's a tough one.
So I go with "ytterbium"...
(Sheldon:)...which gets you back to M.
So you go, "Molybdenum."
And I say, "Magnesium."
And you say, "Manganese."
And I say, "Europium."
And you're left with "mendelevium."
And there are no more M's,
because I believe that meitnerium...
(Sheldon:)...should still be called eka-iridium.
So congratulations, you win.
(Sheldon:)Do you wanna go again?